[Music]
at icici bank we offer a comprehensive
suite of innovative financial products
and services to our large client base in
india and across the world
icici bank canada a full-service direct
bank in canada
facilitates bilateral trade and boosts
investments between canada and india
[Music]
our wide gamut of banking solutions for
individual and corporate clients
network of branches and atms
round-the-clock call centers
best-in-class digital platforms and
mobile apps help our clients in
realizing their ambitions
[Music]
our hello canada program
ensures that people coming to canada for
the first time have a bank account at
their fingertips even before they land
we not only offer customized mortgages
remittance solutions and special
products like the student gic program
and unifi
but also provide assistance for nri
banking services
icici bank canada provides a host of
financial solutions to canadian
companies
funds and investors who have existing
business interests in india and to those
who are looking to enter the indian
market
we help them in raising capital
provide loans and commercial real estate
financing and offer traditional trade
and foreign exchange products to manage
their treasury needs
the bank also offers 360 degree
solutions to canadian pension funds
and asset management companies
covering the entire life cycle of their
investments
[Music]
the bank also works closely with icici
foundation across diverse sectors and
programs to build a sustainable future
your continued patronage has ensured
that we are your banker of choice
at icici bank
we aspire to continue enhancing your
banking experience
[Music]